{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": [
        {
          "Question": "Which game features an assassin named Ezio Auditore?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Assassin's Creed II",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Tomb Raider",
            "Uncharted 2",
            "Gears of War 2"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Assassin's Creed II introduces Ezio Auditore as the main protagonist set in Renaissance Italy."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time', who is the main antagonist?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Ganondorf",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Bowser",
            "Dr. Robotnik",
            "Sephiroth"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Ganondorf serves as the primary antagonist, seeking the Triforce to conquer Hyrule."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which of these is not a 'Tomb Raider' game title?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Throne of Eldraine",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Legend",
            "Angel of Darkness",
            "Underworld"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Throne of Eldraine' is not a 'Tomb Raider' game title, but a set in the 'Magic: The Gathering' card game."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Red Dead Redemption 2', who is the leader of the Van der Linde Gang?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Dutch van der Linde",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Arthur Morgan",
            "John Marston",
            "Josiah Trelawny"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Dutch van der Linde is the charismatic and manipulative leader of the gang, guiding them through the Wild West era."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game features protagonist Nathan Drake as a treasure hunter?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Uncharted 2",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "The Last of Us",
            "Horizon Zero Dawn",
            "Bloodborne"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Nathan Drake is the main character in 'Uncharted 2', where he embarks on perilous adventures in search of mythical treasures."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the island where 'Far Cry 3' is set?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Rook Islands",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Liberty City",
            "Arkham City",
            "Los Santos"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The tropical setting of 'Far Cry 3' takes place on the Rook Islands, known for its stunning landscapes and dangerous inhabitants."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which of these is not a playable character in 'God of War' (2018)?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Aloy",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Kratos",
            "Atreus",
            "Baldur"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Aloy is the protagonist of the 'Horizon Zero Dawn' series and is not a playable character in the 'God of War' game."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the main objective in 'Shadow of the Colossus'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Defeat the Colossi",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Collect Artifacts",
            "Unlock Power-Ups",
            "Solve Puzzles"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The game revolves around the protagonist's quest to defeat massive colossi, in the hope of reviving a deceased maiden."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game series features the character Bayek as an assassin?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Assassin's Creed Origins",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Watch Dogs",
            "Dishonored",
            "Metal Gear Solid V"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Bayek is the main character in 'Assassin's Creed Origins', set in ancient Egypt during the formation of the Assassin Brotherhood."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt', what is Geralt's profession?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Witcher",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Bounty Hunter",
            "Mercenary",
            "Blacksmith"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Geralt is a professional monster hunter known as a witcher, proficient in combat and alchemy."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which of these is not a location in the game 'The Last of Us'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Iceland",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Boston",
            "Salt Lake City",
            "Pittsburgh"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Iceland' is not a location featured in 'The Last of Us' game, which mainly takes place across the United States."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the main character's name in the 'Arkham' series of games?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Batman",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Superman",
            "The Joker",
            "Catwoman"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The 'Arkham' series features Batman as the central character, navigating the sprawling and ominous Arkham Asylum and Gotham City."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Horizon Zero Dawn', what are the robotic creatures called?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Machines",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Dinosaurs",
            "Dragons",
            "Mechanoids"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The robotic animals in 'Horizon Zero Dawn' are known as 'Machines', embodying diverse designs and behaviors within the game's post-apocalyptic world."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game stars a protagonist named Kratos and is based on Greek mythology?",
          "TrueAnswer": "God of War",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Devil May Cry",
            "Bayonetta",
            "Dynasty Warriors"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'God of War' features Kratos, a Spartan warrior seeking vengeance against the gods of Olympus within the realm of Greek mythology."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Bioshock Infinite', what is the floating city called?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Columbia",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Rapture",
            "Midgar",
            "Skyrim"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The game is set in the airborne city of 'Columbia', a utopian society hiding dark secrets and political intrigue."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game involves time-traveling as part of its storyline?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Metal Gear Solid V",
            "Resident Evil 4",
            "Dark Souls"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The 'Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time' incorporates time manipulation as a core mechanic, allowing players to rewind and alter events in the game."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the fictional city in the 'Assassin's Creed' series?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Rome",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Athens",
            "Paris",
            "Venice"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The 'Assassin's Creed' series features various historical settings, including 'Rome', where significant events unfold within the Assassin-Templar conflict."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game emphasizes environmental puzzles and platforming elements?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Prince of Persia: The Two Thrones",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Call of Duty: Modern Warfare",
            "Splinter Cell: Blacklist",
            "Destiny 2"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Prince of Persia: The Two Thrones' showcases challenging environmental puzzles and acrobatic platforming as integral aspects of the gameplay experience."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Darksiders II', who is the main protagonist?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Death",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "War",
            "Fury",
            "Strife"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The main protagonist in 'Darksiders II' is Death, one of the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse, on a mission to clear his brother War's name."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which game allows players to control a character named Aloy in a post-apocalyptic world?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Horizon Zero Dawn",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Detroit: Become Human",
            "Days Gone",
            "The Last of Us Part II"
          ],
          "Explanation": "'Horizon Zero Dawn' unfolds in a post-apocalyptic world where players assume the role of Aloy, a skilled hunter seeking to unravel the mysteries of her origins and the world's fate."
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}